JOHN MIGUEL ANGEL

CUSTOMER SERVICE SPECIALIST

CONTACT



+49 (0) 17620542813

im.mikel@hotmail.com

Aroser Allee 118, Berlin 13407

EDUCATION

Onboard Service Assistant

INEC Flight Academy, Colombia 2013-2015

Customer Relationship Management

Instituto Técnico Superior de Pereira 2014

Hotel Management

SENA, Colombia 2009-2011

SKILLS

Communication

Customer Service

Time Management

Problem Solving

Conflict Management

LANGUAGES

Spanish - Native

German - Proficient

English - Proficient

PROFILE

Multidimensional customer care specialist with 8 years of working experience in delivering customer satisfaction across hospitality, travel, and health industries. Specialized in mitigating human emotions in high-stress, time-sensitive situations and ensuring high customer retention. Driven to create impact in a multinational environment and facilitate exceptional customer experiences.

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Nursing Assistant & Apprentice, Pro Seniore Krankenheim Eichborndamm & Vivantes, Germany

AUG 2020 - PRESENT

- Helping patients effectively manage their routine
- Conveying behavioral concerns and medically relevant symptoms to healthcare staff to optimize care delivery.

Customer Care & Lost and Found Agent, Aeroground,

Germany APR 2019 - OCT 2019

 Resolved customer requests, queries, and complaints by analyzing individual situations and determining best use of resources.

Senior Cabin Crew Member, Luftfahrtgesellschaft Walter,

Germany APR 2017 - MAR 2019

- Resolved passenger situations during flights involving disorderly passengers and medical emergencies.
- Offered personalized assistance to children, elderly, and passengers with special needs.

Flight Attendant, Avianca, Colombia

JUL 2014 - JUN 2016

- Facilitated efficient passenger onboarding process.
- Ensured safety and comfort of customers onboard aircraft.

Sales & Customer Service Agent, Colreservas, Colombia

AUG 2013 - JUL 2014

- Generated monthly sales for the department
- Served as main point of contact for national & international clients

Patient Coordinator, Psicólogos de la Salud, Colombia

SEP 2012 - MAY 2013

- Managed patients' appointments
- · Ensured psychological safety of patients during on-sight visits